<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FootballApp</string>
    <string name="title_top">All-time best 5 players</string>
    <string name="select_top">Please select player</string>
    <string name="image_content_description_top">Player face</string>
    <string name="player_not_selected">Please select one</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Photos</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Videos</string>
    <string name="text_title_main">Football App</string>
    <string name="image_main">Start image</string>
    <string name="title_era">ERA</string>
    <string name="era1_title">The Beginnings</string>
    <string name="image_content_description_era">Football game</string>
    <string name="era2_titel">Football becoming international</string>
    <string name="era3_title">From Amateur to Professional</string>
    <string name="era4_title">Founding of UEFA</string>
    <string name="era5_title">Mass media</string>
    <string name="era6_title">Era of Superstars</string>
    <string name="menu_title_main">Start</string>
    <string name="menu_title_era">Era</string>
    <string name="description_puskas">Hungary\'s most famous player scored in Budapest Honvéd and Real Madrid 514 goals in 539 matches. A World Cup finalist and Olympic champion, he was eight times top scorer in the Hungarian and Spanish leagues.</string>
    <string name="description_pele">The South American wunderkind won the World Cup three times with the Brazilian national side. The former striker capped 92 times holds the record of most scored goals in the Brazilian team with 77 goals. Pelé won with his team FC Santos in 17 years altogether 26 national and international titles.</string>
    <string name="description_maradona">Diega Armando Maradona is considered as one of the best football players in history. He led his Argentinian national team as captain to win the 1986 World Cup. Altogether he participated on four World Cups and scored 34 goals in 91 games.</string>
    <string name="description_ronaldo">Trained by the youth academy of Sportind Lisboa, Cristiano Ronaldo transferred at the age of 18 to Manchester United where he became a world class footballer. He is the only player ever to win the English, Spanish and Italian champions title as well as named Player of the year in all three countries.</string>
    <string name="description_messi">Consider by many experts the greatest player of all times, Lionel Messi is with six wins the record title holder of France Football\'s prestigious Ballon D\'Or award. With FC Barcelona he won among others four Champions League, ten Spanish League, and six Spanish Cup titles.</string>
    <string name="text_decription_main">Football, the most popular sport of the world was created in Britain in the second half of the 19. century and spread across continental Europe and overseas in the 1880\'s and 1890\'s.</string>
    <string name="era1_description">The sport became ever more popular in the private schools and universities of England. In 1857 the first Club for Association Football, FC Sheffield was created. Because of the founding if Football Association (FA) in London in 1863 and the creation of the first football rulebook there, England is considered the birthplace of football.</string>
    <string name="era2_description">On continental Europe football set foot first in Switzerland. From there it was exported to the neighbouring countries: In 1909 the swiss-rooted club Stade Helvétique Marseille won the French championship, the FC Barcelona was founded by swissman Joan Gamper. As the nationalistically oriented Milan Cricket and Football Club didn\'t accept foreigners, swiss and Italian players founded the new club Inter Milan.</string>
    <string name="era3_description">The first professional leagues started in the interwar period. With the introduction of a Profi-League in 1924 Austria became the first nation on continental Europe to have an event for paid players. Three years later the Austrian Football Association initiated the first notable international event for club teams in form of the Central European Cup. This served as a predecessor of today\'s major European Cups like the UEFA Champions League.</string>
    <string name="era4_description">The Union of European Football Associations was founded in 1954 in the Swiss city of Basel. In 1955/56 the UEFA already organized the first European Cup for national champions. In 1960 the European Nation\'s Cup was launched, taking the name UEFA European Championship eight years later.</string>
    <string name="era5_description">The game became in the following years even more popular, the mass media and the development in televised broadcasting lifted the global interest in football. In the qualification phase of Euro 2002 198 national teams were admitted. Currently with 208 nations, the World Football Federation FIFA has more members as countries represented in the United Nations (192).</string>
    <string name="era6_description">Today the popularity of the best footballers is bigger than ever. Players like Messi, Neymar or Ronaldo have more than 100 Million followers on social media. Their influence on the game is huge and they can singlehandedly decide the fate of tournaments.</string>
    <string name="player_puskas">Ferenc Puskás</string>
    <string name="menu_title_top">Top5</string>
    <string name="menu_title_media">Media</string>
    <string name="menu_title_quiz">Quiz</string>
    <string-array name="top_players">
        <item>Player</item>
        <item>Ferenc Puskás</item>
        <item>Pelé</item>
        <item>Diego Maradona</item>
        <item>Cristiano Ronaldo</item>
        <item>Lionel Messi</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="image_content_description_fullscreen">Fullscreen picture</string>
    <string name="image_content_description_gallery3">Stadium</string>
    <string name="image_content_description_gallery4">Brazil match</string>
    <string name="image_content_description_gallery5">Groupama Arena</string>
    <string name="image_content_description_gallery6">Ferencvaros fans</string>
    <string name="title_quiz">QUIZ</string>
    <string name="button_start_quiz">Start Quiz</string>
    <string name="button_text_new_game">New game</string>
    <string name="text_result_bad">Try again</string>
    <string name="text_result_ok">Good result</string>
    <string name="text_result_good">Very good result</string>
    <string name="text_result_perfect">Perfect result</string>
    <string name="description_image_result">Result image</string>
    <string name="text_score">"Score: "</string>
    <string name="text_score_zero">Score: 0</string>
    <string name="button_text_next">Next</string>
    <string name="button_text_result">Finish</string>
    <string name="select_answer">Please select an answer</string>
    <string name="button_text_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="text_question_nr">"Question: "</string>
    <string name="text_answer1_correct">Answer 1 is correct</string>
    <string name="text_answer2_correct">Answer 2 is correct</string>
    <string name="text_answer3_correct">Answer 3 is correct</string>
</resources>